<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Jonathan Rhodes</title>
    <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Jonathan Rhodes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>See you at Bevrijdingsfestival Groningen</title>
      <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2021-05-01-bfg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2021-05-01-bfg/</guid>
      <description>  We&#39;re playing at BevrijdingsFestival Groningen in honour of 76 years of freedom in The Netherlands. A sweet list of local acts will be playing, like Them Dirty Dimes. The event will be live streamed here. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey Sister is out now!</title>
      <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2021-01-08-hey-sister/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2021-01-08-hey-sister/</guid>
      <description>  Our new single Hey Sister is out now. You can listen to it right here.   For the full press kit, click here. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grunnsonic Livestream</title>
      <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2021-01-07-grunnsonic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2021-01-07-grunnsonic/</guid>
      <description>On Friday January 15th we&#39;ll be playing Grunnsonic. The event aired as a livestream on January 15th 2021. You can watch it below.  The line-up has been put together by POPgroningen, the pop-organization of the Province of Groningen, in collaboration with ESNS. Local acts present themselves to the public and music professionals during ESNS in an entirely digital program. The program consists of showcases and interviews with the selected acts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nominee Best Talent ESNS Popgala Noord</title>
      <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2021-01-07-popgala/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2021-01-07-popgala/</guid>
      <description>We&#39;re proud to announce we&#39;ve been nominated for Best Talent at the Popgala Noord (part of the Eurosonic Noorderslag festival).  Popgala Noord is the award show for pop culture of the Northern part of the Netherlands. Especially the three provinces Drenthe, Friesland and Groningen. Popgala Noord 2021 will be a digital event and it will take place on january 12 at 17:00. The show will be recorded in Vera and will be broadcasted on Podium TV and the digital channels of the Leeuwarder Courant and the Dagblad van het Noorden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Participant of Hit The North</title>
      <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2021-01-07-hit-the-north/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2021-01-07-hit-the-north/</guid>
      <description>We&#39;re happy to announce we&#39;ve been selected for the Hit the North talent development program.  Hit the North is a unique collaboration between festivals, media, venues and educative institutions from the north of the Netherlands. Hit the North is established to stimulate professional talent development in Groningen, Friesland and Drenthe. Northern pop culture is unique, but often artists experience many difficulties that hold them back from really breaking through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winner of the 2020 POPgroningen Talent Award</title>
      <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2020-12-12-talent-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/news/2020-12-12-talent-award/</guid>
      <description>  On Saturday December 12th 2020 we won the POPgroningen Talent Award. In their feedback the jury said that we were able to  &amp;ldquo;convince with a solid show. The tight teamwork and comfortable stage presence made the scouts believe that the band are ready to enter the Dutch music scene&amp;rdquo;.   Read more here (Dutch)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
